blogmint.com 2018-02-07

# Privacy Policy - Blogmint

This Privacy Policy explains how www.blogmint.com (hereinafter referred to as the "Website") owned, managed and operated by Blogmint Digital Private Limited (hereinafter referred to "Blogmint") collects, uses, discloses and protects the Personal Information obtained explicitly through the Website, as well as other information collected automatically without direct submission by you. "Personal Information" is information that enables anyone to contact you. Your full name, address, IP address, e-mail address are examples of personal information. 

You may need to provide the Website your Personal Information during the course of using some services of the Website; for instance, while registering on the Website. If you do not intend to provide us with such Personal Information then you may not be able to use certain functionalities of the Website.

Any Personal Information that you provide to "Blogmint" via this Website will be used only for such purposes and/or activities as are mentioned at the point of gathering such information, or otherwise stated, for instance to respond to your queries or comments, to register your user account, or to otherwise provide any information to you.

Blogmint may use the information submitted by you to send you e-mails that you have opted-in for, and for administrative purposes. Your email address is deleted from Website’s database when you unsubscribe from the website. Blogmint does not make these e-mail addresses available to any third party without your consent. Website gives you the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. Website will never automatically send you information/offers you do not want unless you choose to receive them.

When you use the site, Website’s servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) may collect information indirectly and automatically about your activities on the Website; for instance by way of cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a User's browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a User's computer hard drive. This anonymous information is maintained distinctly and is not linked to the Personal Information you submit to Website. The anonymous information will be used for Website’s understanding of how the Website is used and for other statistical purposes, for system administration and to personalize your experience. Website may also collect information related to the referring URL, access times, browser type, and your IP address for tracking usage patterns and, if necessary, deny service in accordance with our Terms.

Blogmint may disclose aggregated information about the use of the Website, but it will never contain Personal Information. Blogmint does not disclose Personal Information to third parties in the normal course of operations without your consent. However, in situations when Blogmint is legally obligated to disclose information to the government or other third parties, Blogmint will do so.

Website implements standard measures to protect against unauthorized access to and unlawful interception of Personal Information. However, no internet site can fully eliminate security risks.

Website reserves the right to modify all or some of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. An updated policy will be uploaded on the website upon any change or amendment. Blogmint will use information only in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected unless we have received explicit authorization from the appropriate user(s) to do otherwise.

* * *

### Contact Us

If you have any queries about our privacy pledge, or want to know more about the above stated terms and conditions, then please contact us at:

Phone No: +91 120 4601883  
Email: [reachus@blogmint.com](mailto:reachus@blogmint.com)

**Gedung Tifa, Jalan Kuningan Barat 1 No.26,  
Mampang Prapatan, Daerah Khusus Ibukota  
Jakarta 12710, Indonesia ** **Logix Techno Park, Tower B, 4th Floor  
Sector - 127, Noida  
Uttar Pradesh, INDIA. **

**3rd Floor, Sahukar's Building #721,  
CMH Road, Indranagar 1st Stage,  
Bengaluru - 560038. **
